autofurnish.com 2019-03-29

# Privacy Policy

### **Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is an electronic record in the form of an electronic contract formed under the information technology act, 2000 and the rules made there under and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic documents / records in various statutes as amended by the information technology act, 2000. This privacy policy does not require any physical, electronic or digital signature.

Auto Furnish is committed to safeguarding your privacy and we understand the importance you place on the privacy and security of your Identifiable Information. "Identifiable Information" means, as the term suggests, information that identifies you, including name, address, telephone number or e-mail address and financial information that is collected by Auto Furnish through this website.

Please read the following policy to understand how your Identifiable Information collected through the Auto Furnish website(s) will be treated. This Privacy Policy may be updated or changed from time-to-time, so please check back periodically. Your use of this website represents your acceptance of the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

       **•**  To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

       **•**  To improve our website in order to better serve you.

       **•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

       **•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

       **•**  To quickly process your transactions.

       **•**  To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

       **•**  To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**How do we protect your information?**

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

We do not use an SSL certificate

       **•**  We do not need an SSL because:

We have payment gateway which is SSL secured.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**We use cookies to:**

       **•**  Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.

       **•**  Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

       **•**  Keep track of advertisements.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. It won't affect the user's experience that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.

However, you will still be able to place orders.

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

**Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

       **•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

**Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.**

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

**We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.**

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

**It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking**

**Fair Information Practices**

**The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.**

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

**We will notify you via email**

**       • Within 1 business day**

**We will notify the users via in-site notification**

**       • Within 7 business days**

**We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.**

**CAN SPAM Act**

**The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.**

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**       • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions**

**       • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.**

**       • Send you additional information related to your product and/or service**

**       • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.**

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:**

**       • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.**

**       • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.**

**       • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.**

**       • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.**

**       • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.**

**       • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.**

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at**

**       • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.**

**and we will promptly remove you from  ALL correspondence.**

**Contacting Us**

**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.**

**http://www.autofurnish.com**

**A-73 Ground Floor, Malviya Nagar**

**Delhi, Delhi 110017**

**India**
